[
  {
    "question": "What is the main purpose of lists in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "To organize content in a structured way",
      "To change font size",
      "To add colors",
      "To create hyperlinks"
    ],
    "answer": "To organize content in a structured way"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can an ordered list be displayed in reverse order?",
    "options": [
      "<ol reversed>",
      "<ol reverse>",
      "<ol type=\"R\">",
      "<ol start=\"0\">"
    ],
    "answer": "<ol reversed>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which attribute is used to start an ordered list from a specific number?",
    "options": [
      "type",
      "start",
      "value",
      "count"
    ],
    "answer": "start"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which attribute is used to make a custom sequence like alphabet or Roman number format in an ordered list?",
    "options": [
      "type",
      "start",
      "value",
      "count"
    ],
    "answer": "type"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is used to create a main category with subcategories in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "<ul> only",
      "<ol> only",
      "Nested list",
      "<dl> only"
    ],
    "answer": "Nested list"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is used to create ordered list in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "<ol>",
      "<ul>",
      "<li>",
      "<dl>"
    ],
    "answer": "<ol>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is used to create Unordered list in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "<ol>",
      "<ul>",
      "<li>",
      "<dl>"
    ],
    "answer": "<ul>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is used to create a definition list in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "<dl>",
      "<ul>",
      "<ol>",
      "<li>"
    ],
    "answer": "<dl>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tag is used to define each item inside a list?",
    "options": [
      "<li>",
      "<ol>",
      "<ul>",
      "<dl>"
    ],
    "answer": "<li>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tag is not used in definition list?",
    "options": [
      "<dt>",
      "<dd>",
      "<li>",
      "<dl>"
    ],
    "answer": "<li>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following correctly creates a nested list in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "<ul><li>Fruits</li><ul><li>Apple</li></ul></ul>",
      "<ul><ul>Fruits<li>Apple</li></ul></ul>",
      "<ol>Fruits<ul>Apple</ul></ol>",
      "<dl><dt>Fruits</dt><ul>Apple</ul></dl>"
    ],
    "answer": "<ul><li>Fruits</li><ul><li>Apple</li></ul></ul>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax for an HTML comment?",
    "options": [
      "<!-- This is a comment -->",
      "/* This is a comment */",
      "// This is a comment",
      "** This is a comment **"
    ],
    "answer": "<!-- This is a comment -->"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements about HTML comments is true?",
    "options": [
      "Comments are visible on the webpage",
      "Comments help developers explain code",
      "Comments are executed by the browser",
      "Comments replace the <p> tag"
    ],
    "answer": "Comments help developers explain code"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are HTML tags case sensitive?",
    "options": [
      "Yes, <HTML> and <html> are different tags",
      "No, HTML tags are not case sensitive",
      "Only Some tags as case sensitive",
      "All of the Above."
    ],
    "answer": "No, HTML tags are not case sensitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a nested tag in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "A tag that is written inside another tag",
      "A tag that is self-closing",
      "A tag that cannot contain text",
      "A tag that starts with </>"
    ],
    "answer": "A tag that is written inside another tag"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main purpose of HTML entities?",
    "options": [
      "To display special characters.",
      "To make text bold",
      "To create links",
      "To add comments"
    ],
    "answer": "To display special characters."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax for an HTML entity?",
    "options": [
      "&entity_name;",
      "&entity_name",
      "<entity_name>",
      "#entity_name;"
    ],
    "answer": "&entity_name;"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a numeric HTML entity?",
    "options": [
      "&70;",
      "&#60;",
      "&#x30C;",
      "&#copy;"
    ],
    "answer": "&#60;"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a hexadecimal HTML entity?",
    "options": [
      "&70;",
      "&#60;",
      "&#x30C;",
      "&#copy;"
    ],
    "answer": "&#x30C;"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many main types of HTML entities are there?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  }
]